I will become the bride of the person
who proposed to my older sister.
Baron Shaderan has two daughters.
One is cheerful and sociable,
with soft golden hair.
Anastasia, the older sister,
is like a princess.
The other is tall, like a boy.
All the tattered younger sister,
Marie, does is read books.
Episode 1 "I Could Never Replace My Sister"
The Shaderan family is poor.
Every day there is a mountain
of housework to be done.
And meals for the family
must be prepared as well.
Then there's Father's work, balancing the
accounts and signing documents in his stead.
But it's all right.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
I'm certain it will be a good day.
Sister, you're amazing! You look beautiful!
Thank you, Cedric.
And your hair is so fluffy!
Everyone!
Thank you for gathering here today!
Here is the star of the day's events!
What?
I see.
This is a debut party for my sister to find
someone to marry among the great houses.
I am pleased to make your acquaintance.
You are just as beautiful as they say.
Just because it's my birthday...
it doesn't mean that I'd become
the star of the evening.
Why was I born so horribly ugly?
Pardon me, miss.
I apologize for startling you.
I've been invited to the birthday party.
The entrance is through there.
Thank you, Miss Maid.
Master, this personage is not a servant.
What?
The Shaderan family has one maid,
a 60 year-old woman.
They have no other servants.
Really? Then...
She must be one of the two daughters.
I have been terribly rude.
Please, forgive me, my lady.
Could it be...
Are you from the Ipsandros Republic?
Y-Yes. My mother was a traveling
performer from Ipsandros.
What of it?
Oh, I knew it! And your clothes are
traditional Ipsandrian formal wear, aren't they?
Are you knowledgable about
Ipsandrian culture?
I wouldn't say I'm knowledgable. I only
know what I've learned from books.
How unusual.
To think that you studied Ips culture
in a country as insular as this one.
Oh but...
Once a person realizes the depth of
Ipsandrian technology and culture,
they are instantly captivated by it!
I am one such person myself!
Exactly!
My personal wardrobe is made of Ips silk, of
course, but I insist that my underclothes are too!
I won't compromise on that!
You are quite fashionable, sir.
Personally, I love stories from Ipsandros.
Do you know the story,
"The Raggedy Red Cat"?
Yes, of course!
Raggedy, the abandoned cat,
travels with a kindly wanderer and
grows stronger along the way.
I have red hair and I'm
always in tatters, so...
A woman who makes a show of her
knowledge is an embarrassment!
I-I'm so terribly sorry! I've
behaved in such a shameful manner!
Shameful? In what way?
W-Well, I...
Please excuse me!
Please, wait!
Eyes more beautiful than any star...
How can he be so wonderful?
And this wonderful man is here
to propose to my sister.
Compared to her, I am...
H-Have I offended you in some way?
If it's because I mistook you for a servant,
I'll apologize as many times as it takes.
You've done nothing wrong, sir.
Your clothes...
Is there an extraordinary
circumstance behind this?
No. I'm simply not lovely, that's all.
I have enjoyed speaking
with you tonight.
You are beautiful.
The evening's star is in the salon.
Please go and enjoy yourself there.
Those were the words I'd
always longed to hear.
So why... why do I feel so sad?
To the eldest daughter of Baron Shaderan,
Lady Anastasia,
Beautiful lady, I would like to welcome you into the family of Count Granado as the wife of Kyros Granado. Even a day's delay is too long.
One month after that terrible birthday,
a letter with a marriage proposal arrived.
He's highly influential!
You'll be marrying upward!
Count Granado will inherit
the title of Duke one day.
And he's exceedingly wealthy, too!
You'll be able to live more lavishly
than the monarch of a small country!
But I...
Marie! Hurry up and pen a reply!
Inform our relatives and
any neighboring nobility!
Yes, I will at once.
I'm going to be married.
And to someone whose face
I don't even remember.
I've heard that Count Granado is a
bad-tempered eccentric who hates women.
Please, don't worry. The proposal
letter was so passionate.
I'm certain that he will cherish you.
But more importantly, there's
something I'd like for you to see!
Oh, how wonderful!
Marie, you're tall, so
it suits you perfectly!
Wh-What is this?
Clothes made for a woman to dress as a man!
I suppose this is what's meant
by "asking for the moon"!
I love to see beautiful women dressed
as men and I love dashing ladies!
I made all of this myself!
I-I see.
Please keep it a secret
from mother and father.
They found some things before
and threw it all away.
Sister, I didn't know you had
these interests. How amazing!
If for some reason the Shaderan family
could no longer sustain itself...
If one day I had to work too...
I thought that I might open
a shop in the royal capital.
Say, Marie...
please make the most of your
skills and do work that you love.
My older sister was beloved by everyone.
I loved her too.
But on her way to marry Count Granado...
she lost her life in an accident.
Sister...
A long time ago...
she would often read
"The Raggedy Red Cat" to me.
You should have been the one to die.
Why is it you and not she who is alive?
You killed Anastasia, didn't you?
It's your fault! You murderer!
You and that red hair of yours!
Will you stop? You'll leave marks.
She should be scarred! So scarred that
no one will ever look at her face again!
No.
Marie will take Anastasia's place and
go to the home of Count Granado.
Me? Take my sister's place?
Don't worry, Marie.
I know that you are a hideous little thing.
Th-Then why...
We've sold everything that was
sent to us for the betrothal.
We don't have the money to buy it all back.
The count will be heartbroken at the
loss of Anastasia. Exploit that.
Even if it's just one night of comfort,
once you create a connection, we've won.
A night of comfort?
Be Anastasia's replacement, Marie.
That is how you can atone.
Atone?
What crime have I committed?
Oh, that's right.
Being born as lowly me... that was my mistake.
Be docile and amenable, Marie.
I will.
If the count dissolves the betrothal,
return home immediately.
I will.
I'm saying these things for your sake,
failure that you are. You understand that?
Yes. Thank you.
Not even your smile is lovable.
It would have been far better for you
to have died instead of Anastasia.
Today, I go to the man who
proposed to my older sister...
to be his bride.
What is the meaning of this?!
Let us into the palace! We
sent a letter in advance!
Y-You say that, but...
The letter arrived only this morning.
To call that advance notice puts
us all in a difficult position.
There is no point in speaking
to you! Bring the count here!
You're just a servant!
Father!
Baron Shaderan, I must ask that you leave.
This woman...
I-I'm so sorry! My father
has been terribly rude!
That bow of contrition was so fluid.
I'm truly so very sorry.
Y-You're... No. Are you Lady Marie?
Y-Yes. I am Marie, daughter
of the House of Shaderan.
Though I don't look anything
like my older sister.
Tomas, take a message to
the master immediately.
Y-Yes, miss!
Thank you for coming.
I am the head chamberlain, Mio.
Lady Marie, please come inside.
You can't be serious!
Send Marie Shaderan away!
B-But, Master...
The one I proposed to was Anastasia!
Not her younger sister!
Oh, Anastasia. If only I'd
whisked you away that night.
Master.
What?
If it's about Marie Shaderan,
I've told you to—
M-My name is Marie.
It is, um... It is an
honor to meet you today.
L-Lord Kyros?
Oh, how could this have happened?
I never imagined that Count Granado
was the man I met that night.
A pleasure to meet you, Count Granado.
My eldest daughter Anastasia's unfortunate
accident brought our marriage talks to a halt,
and your lordship must be heartbroken.
And so I have brought Anastasia's
sister by blood, Marie.
Marie? You're Marie?
This is, indeed, Marie.
She compares quite unfavorably
with Anastasia, but—
Master, your expression has
become quite frightening.
That was unseemly of me. Please spend the
night in comfort here in the palace.
I shall prepare a room immediately.
Um, where has my father gone?
He is meeting with the master.
In the meantime, why not
relax with a cup of tea?
What a lovely aroma.
Could it be that this is from
the Republic of Ipsandros?
How impressive that you know that.
I once read that they put spices in their tea
and drink it for their health in that country.
It's ginger and cinnamon.
They go well with tea from this country too.
Ipsandros is truly amazing to be able
to create a tea as delicious as this!
H-Have I said something strange?
Pardon me. I was just thinking that
you are quite adorable, Lady Marie.
Adorable?
Yes, coming.
Count Kyros Granado!
I'm so terribly sorry!
For what?
W-We have been unforgivably discourteous.
I-Is my father...
He left.
I said, "There's no need to
return the betrothal gifts.
Offer them to Miss Anastasia's
grave for me," and he was gone.
What?
Wait!
There's something I want to ask you.
Wh-What is it?
Marie, has your family been abusing you?
Abusing me?
It's true that they didn't
treat me with much affection.
But that's because they were
training me, isn't it?
It... wasn't that.
The reason that Father and
Mother are strict with me
is so that a know-nothing
like me can survive.
I don't know how it may look
to you, your lordship, but...
It's Kyros.
My name is Kyros.
I don't like being called by
my family name or my title.
I want you to call me by my first name.
Of course... Lord Kyros.
Going back to what you were saying...
If you weren't being mistreated, then why
were you dressed like that on your birthday?
That's because...
Clothes like those are normally
worn by widows and nuns.
It's a color meant to turn men away.
Are you going to become a nun?
No.
Then, do you simply hate men?
Then, did you act as a foil for
your sister because you wanted to?
Are you unhappy in the Shaderan family?
Marie, I can't understand
anything if you don't speak.
It wasn't a life I wanted.
But I never entertained any
hope of escaping that place.
I hate this. This time here.
I...
am not lovely, you see?
I see.
Mio, take Marie away!
Yes, master.
I'm being cast out, aren't I?
It was strange that they let
me into the palace at all.
Lady Marie.
Shall we?
I've already arranged for a
bath and a change of clothes.
What? What is she talking about?
Wh-What is this? Could it
be that this is the bath?!
How much firewood and water does this use?
Cleaning it must be difficult too!
I see! They're telling me
to chop firewood and clean!
That will wash away all the
discourteousness I've shown him.
What a magnanimous man.
Oh, I've been waiting for you!
I am Tunika. I am the keeper
of the baths for the count.
Lady Marie, she knows many bathing methods
and massages that are good
for health and beauty.
She is also well-versed in medicines
and their effects. A true beauty pro.
A beauty pro?
A professional.
Wh-When did you do this?
Lady Marie, if Tunika displeases you too
greatly, please feel free to slap her.
Huh? What?
But I'm going to be cleaning the baths now.
Oh, no. It isn't the bath that will
be beautified. It's you, Lady Marie!
Wh-What?
It smells so nice.
I've added salt, honey, and citrus fruits.
I'll have you reborn, all
soft and sparklingly clean.
Reborn?
A chrysalis is meant to turn
into a butterfly, you know?
Who will... turn into what?
What a beautiful person. Who is she?
Marie.
Liu Liu!
Right here!
I can hear you.
Kyros, you're more swayed by
good looks than I thought.
Good looks?
Please do this properly, mother.
The head of the family's approval is
necessary for a betrothal between nobles,
which means it rests
entirely with you, mother.
Mother?
Lord Kyros mentioned that his mother
was from Ipsandros, didn't he?
No good. She's lacking.
Mother...
She is overwhelmingly lacking in confidence.
The future wife of a duke must
stand proudly, noble and strong.
At least, she must before
the wedding day.
The real work starts now.
I'll do what I can to help.
Thank you, mother!
Congratulations, Lady Marie.
Thank you.
Wait. Congratulations? For what?
The duchess has approved your
betrothal to Lord Kyros.
Now, you are officially Count
Kyros Granado's fiancée.
F-Fiancée?!
Congratulations on your betrothal,
Lord Kyros, Lady Marie!
So my son is finally getting married!
At last I can set down these burdens.
Liu Liu, it's far too soon for that.
We haven't even held the
betrothal ceremony yet.
That's true enough.
I know! Let's dispatch a messenger so that
we can decide on a date for the ceremony!
Um, excuse me...
I... I can't do this!
What?
Wait, wait!
Why has the count proposed to me?
I may be my sister's replacement, but a
tattered mess like me could never be loved.
My life here is like a dream. It's
sure to disappear at any moment.
Next time, "Marie, I Want to Marry You."
Episode 2 " Marie, I Want to Marry You"
P-Please come and watch.